Finding Aid for the North American New Music Festival Archive, 1983-1995
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Promotion, publicity, and news clippings 1983-1995, II.; Folders 239-385
  - 1985, C.; Folders 263-280
    - Young, Kenneth Spell is woven in rich tones by Danish Trio, in Buffalo News, April 16, 1985, 2 leaves (Box 5, Folder 271)
    - Trotter, Herman Dazzling centerpiece for a varied concert, in Buffalo News, April 17, 1985, 2 leaves (Box 5, Folder 272)
    - Besecker, Bill Jenkins, Bright take note of the infuence of jazz, [source unidentified], April 17, 1985, 2 leaves (Box 5, Folder 273)
    - Trotter, Herman Just like old times: percussion ensemble, Bergamo reunited, in Buffalo News, April 18, 1985, 2 leaves (Box 5, Folder 274)
    - Young, Kenneth The music is easy in cabaret setting, in Buffalo News, April 18, 1985, 2 leaves (Box 5, Folder 275)
    - Putnam, Thomas Works by avant-garde masters Brown and Cage, in Buffalo News, April 19, 1985, 2 leaves (Box 5, Folder 276)
    - Trotter, Herman High-tech soprano: something really new, in Buffalo News, April 20, 1985, 2 leaves (Box 5, Folder 277)
    - Stiller, Andrew New music festival amplifies needlessly, in Buffalo News, April 21, 1985, 2 leaves (Box 5, Folder 278)
    - Trotter, Herman Festival ends on a dreadfully slow note, in Buffalo News, April 22, 1985, 5 leaves (Box 5, Folder 279)
      Published review, note from author, and copy of marked draft of review
    - [State University of New York at Buffalo] New music festival, in Reporter, April 25, 1985, 2 leaves (Box 5, Folder 280)
  - 1986, D.; Folders 281-301
    - North American New Music Festival North American New Music Festival: April 10-20, 1986, [program booklet], circa April 1, 1986, 28 p.: ill., ports.; 28 cm. (Box 5, Folder 281)
    - Trotter, Herman Growing UB new music festival putting Buffalo back in forefront, in Buffalo News, April 6, 1986, 2 leaves (Box 5, Folder 282)
    - Potter, M. Grosvenor Nils loves N.Y. and vice versa, in Buffalo News, circa April 11, 1986, 2 leaves (Box 5, Folder 283)
    - Trotter, Herman Lukas Foss returns to help blaze another new-music trail, in Buffalo News, April 11, 1986, 2 leaves (Box 5, Folder 284)
    - Stiller, Andrew Despite cacti, music was not at all sticky, in Buffalo News, April 12, 1986, 2 leaves (Box 5, Folder 285)
    - Putnam, Thomas In UB concert, EAR proves equal to wide array of compositions, in Buffalo News, circa April 13, 1986, 2 leaves (Box 5, Folder 286)
    - Stiller, Andrew Harpsichord is a star at recital in gallery, in Buffalo News, April 13, 1986, 2 leaves (Box 5, Folder 287)
    - Stiller, Andrew 'Antigone-legend' is masterpiece of structured pianism and mime, in Buffalo News, circa April 14, 1986, 2 leaves (Box 5, Folder 288)
    - Stiller, Andrew Debut of Rzewski's 'To the earth' chimes simplicity via clay pots, in Buffalo News, circa April 15, 1986, 2 leaves (Box 5, Folder 289)
    - Young, Kenneth UB faculty deserves high marks for musical tribute to Thomson, in Buffalo News, April 15, 1986, 2 leaves (Box 5, Folder 290)
    - Stiller, Andrew Montague percussion piece hard to beat, in Buffalo News, April 16, 1986, 2 leaves (Box 5, Folder 291)
    - Trotter, Herman Rorem works entertain but seem recycled, in Buffalo News, April 16, 1986, 2 leaves (Box 5, Folder 292)
    - Putnam, Thomas Pittsburgh ensemble comes up tame, in Buffalo News, April 17, 1986, 2 leaves (Box 5, Folder 293)
    - Stiller, Andrew Two top pianists chopstick through a ho-hum program, in Buffalo News, April 18, 1986, 2 leaves (Box 5, Folder 294)
    - Putnam, Thomas 'Kid copy' is electric even in power failure, in Buffalo News, April 19, 1986, 2 leaves (Box 5, Folder 295)
    - Putnam, Thomas Pianist attuned to modern landscapes, in Buffalo News, April 20, 1986, 2 leaves (Box 5, Folder 296)
    - Stiller, Andrew UB concert computes high-tech program, in Buffalo News, April 20, 1986, 2 leaves (Box 5, Folder 297)
    - Stiller, Andrew Brass displays usual shine for Amherst Quartet, in Buffalo News, circa April 21, 1986, 2 leaves (Box 5, Folder 298)
    - Young, Kenneth Spectrum ensemble performs with flair, in Buffalo News, April 21, 1986, 2 leaves (Box 5, Folder 299)
    - Trotter, Herman Nancarrow's piano works stir call to 'play it again', in Buffalo News, April 21, 1986, 2 leaves (Box 5, Folder 300)
    - [State University of New York at Buffalo] New music festival, [captioned photo feature], in Reporter, April 24, 1986, 2 leaves (Box 5, Folder 301)
  - 1987, E.; Folders 302-320
    - North American New Music Festival North American New Music Festival: April 21-30, 1987, [program booklet], circa April 15, 1987, 24 p.: ill., ports.; 28 cm. (Box 5, Folder 302)
    - State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Dept. April music: North American New Music Festival 1987, [flyer], circa April 15, 1987, 1 leaf (Box 5, Folder 303)
    - State University of New York at Buffalo. News Bureau North American New Music Festival at UB April 21-30, [news release], April 16, 1987, 4 leaves (Box 5, Folder 304)
    - Trotter, Herman New music festival opens Tuesday, in Buffalo News, circa April 19, 1987, 4 leaves (Box 5, Folder 305)
    - Chon, Richard 'Mainstream' warms to Glass works, in Buffalo News, April 22, 1987, 2 leaves (Box 5, Folder 306)
    - Trotter, Herman Canadian flutist exports exquisite talents, in Buffalo News, April 23, 1987, 2 leaves (Box 5, Folder 307)
    - Gasser, Alan Modern program sparkles in hands of Canadian flutist, in Spectator (Toronto), April 23, 1987, 1 leaf (Box 5, Folder 308)
    - Chon, Richard A new music festival composer finds musicality..., [article fragment], in Buffalo News, April 24, 1987, 2 leaves (Box 5, Folder 309)
    - Trotter, Herman Music festival hears the Dorian Wind Quintet perform at peak level, in Buffalo News, April 24, 1987, 2 leaves (Box 5, Folder 310)
    - Chon, Richard Percussion program delights at festival, in Buffalo News, April 25, 1987, 2 leaves (Box 5, Folder 311)
    - Trotter, Herman Cage's presence enhances 3 'spacey' concert, in Buffalo News, April 26, 1987, 2 leaves (Box 5, Folder 312)
    - Young, Kenneth Mikhashoff and Dick give virtuoso efforts, in Buffalo News, April 27, 1987, 2 leaves (Box 5, Folder 313)
    - Putnam, Thomas Past innovators' works get spotlight, in Buffalo News, April 27, 1987, 2 leaves (Box 5, Folder 314)
    - Chon, Richard Hallwalls presents some fine music, indeed, in Buffalo News, April 27, 1987, 2 leaves (Box 5, Folder 315)
    - Trotter, Herman Mini concert is treat with Latin rhythms, in Buffalo News, April 28, 1987, 2 leaves (Box 5, Folder 316)
    - Roger Parris 'Buffalo's newest music' attracts crowd, in Buffalo News, April 28, 1987, 2 leaves (Box 5, Folder 317)
    - Putnam, Thomas Strong feeling shapes composer's work, in Buffalo News, circa April 29, 1987, 2 leaves (Box 5, Folder 318)
    - Trotter, Herman Philharmonic, Druckman close UB's new music festival, in Buffalo News, April 30, 1987, 2 leaves (Box 5, Folder 319)
    - Parris, Roger Computer music generates real excitement, in Buffalo News, April 30, 1987, 2 leaves (Box 5, Folder 320)
  - 1988, F.; Folders 321-325
    - Composers' Forum Inc. Composers' forum network news, vol. V, no. 4, Winter 1987, 8 pages (Box 6, Folder 321)
    - North American New Music Festival North American New Music Festival: March 10-19, 1988, [program booklet], circa March 1, 1988, 24 p.: ill., ports.; 28 cm. (Box 6, Folder 322)
      3 copies: 1 with cover autographed by Lou (Harrison), 1 with cover autographed by Elliott (Carter), one with additional program notes inserted.
    - State University of New York at Buffalo. News Bureau Sixth annual North American New Music Festival set for March 10-19, [news release], circa March 1, 1988, 6 leaves (Box 6, Folder 323)
    - Pettit, Stephen Optimistic airs: upstate and upbeat, in London Times, April 30, 1987, 1 leaf (Box 6, Folder 324)
    - Porter, Andrew Two festivals, in New Yorker, April 18, 1988, 3 leaves (Box 6, Folder 325)
  - 1989, G.; Folders 326-329
    - North American New Music Festival North American New Music Festival: April 11-20, 1989, [program booklet], circa April 1, 1989, 24 p.: ill., ports.; 28 cm. (Box 6, Folder 326)
    - North American New Music Festival Seventh annual North American New Music Festival: April 11-20, 1989, circa April 1, 1989, 1 poster: printed in black ink on yellow paper; 43 x 28 cm. (Box 6, Folder 327)
      Daily program schedule printed on reverse.
    - Composers' Forum Inc. Composers' forum network news, vol. 7, no. 1, Spring 1989, 8 pages (Box 6, Folder 328)
    - Chon, Richard George Crumb's imaginative music opens new music festival, in Buffalo News, April 12, 1989, 2 leaves (Box 6, Folder 329)
  - 1990, H.; Folders 330-356
    - [State University of New York at Buffalo] North American New Music Festival, in A and L news, vol. 4, no. 1, November 1989, 2 leaves (Box 6, Folder 330)
    - North American New Music Festival North American New Music Festival: March 31-April 8, 1990, [program booklet], circa March 24, 1990, 32 p.: ill., ports.; 28 cm. (Box 6, Folder 331)
    - Trotter, Herman New music has its days: burgeoning festival spreads over 10 sites, in Buffalo News, March 25, 1990, 4 leaves (Box 6, Folder 332)
    - Albright-Knox Art Gallery Film for music for film, [postcard], circa March 25, 1990, 1 postcard (Box 6, Folder 333)
    - Waterhouse, Robert You don't hear it on radio: a feast of new music: festival's menu brings exciting events to UB, in Reporter, March 29, 1990, 2 leaves (Box 6, Folder 334)
    - Trotter, Herman Philharmonic offers something for everyone, in Buffalo News, April 1, 1990, 2 leaves (Box 6, Folder 335)
    - Trotter, Herman Blum's voice steals show again, in Buffalo News, April 2, 1990, 2 leaves (Box 6, Folder 336)
    - Young, Kenneth 4 composers perform sonorous works, in Buffalo News, April 2, 1990, 2 leaves (Box 6, Folder 337)
    - Gaub, Eugene Unconventional setting yields fascinating results, in Buffalo News, April 2, 1990, 2 leaves (Box 6, Folder 338)
    - Trotter, Herman New 'Crane' competes with four music pioneers, in Buffalo News, April 3, 1990, 2 leaves (Box 6, Folder 339)
    - Putnam, Thomas Old poems set to new music prove to be hauntingly beautiful, in Buffalo News, April 3, 1990, 2 leaves (Box 6, Folder 340)
    - Hopkins, Michael Sun Ra coming to Marquee, April 3, 1990, 2 leaves (Box 6, Folder 341)
    - Huntington, Richard Brose's films lose out to force of music, in Buffalo News, April 4, 1990, 2 leaves (Box 6, Folder 342)
    - Trotter, Herman Final work soars in white heat: Montague's 'Phrygia' is creation of great originality, in Buffalo News, April 5, 1990, 2 leaves (Box 6, Folder 343)
    - Trotter, Herman An example of the 'Emperor's new clothes', in Buffalo News, April 6, 1990, 2 leaves (Box 6, Folder 344)
    - Artistic differences, [Author, source unidentified], circa April 6, 1990, 2 leaves (Box 6, Folder 345)
    - Besecker, Bill Sun Ra and Arkestra rise to the occasion: improvisational band combines traditional jazz with far-out theater, in Buffalo News, April 7, 1990, 2 leaves (Box 6, Folder 346)
    - Putnam, Thomas Young blends the art of Zen, easy-listening minimalism: timelessness prevails as the drone goes on, in Buffalo News, April 8, 1990, 2 leaves (Box 6, Folder 347)
    - Young, Kenneth Performance style conjures up '60s avant-garde spirit, in Buffalo News, April 8, 1990, 2 leaves (Box 6, Folder 348)
    - Trotter, Herman Concert is marked by some oddities: ex-colleague pickets outside, in Buffalo News, April 8, 1990, 2 leaves (Box 6, Folder 349)
    - Trotter, Herman 'OH, LOIS!' concludes concert with a bouyant [sic], super flourish, in Buffalo News, April 8, 1990, 2 leaves (Box 6, Folder 350)
    - Sedlak, Lynna Piano works go from surreal to super, in Buffalo News, April 9, 1990, 2 leaves (Box 6, Folder 351)
    - Trotter, Herman Finnisy humors his listeners: but performance's climax remains open to question, in Buffalo News, April 9, 1990, 2 leaves (Box 6, Folder 352)
    - Gaub, Eugene Pianist captures best of Beatles in melodies, in Buffalo News, April 9, 1990, 2 leaves (Box 6, Folder 353)
    - Young, Kenneth Festival takes on a local look: Buffalo composers use nature theme in new works, in Buffalo News, April 9, 1990, 2 leaves (Box 6, Folder 354)
    - Wohlfahrt, Hans-Theodor Wie man einen Satten Konzertflüngel füttert: das North American New Music Festival: Impressionen aus Buffalo, in Neue Musikzeitung, circa May 15, 2001, 1 leaf (Box 6, Folder 355)
    - Wohlfahrt, Hans-Theodor Im Schweigen atmen die Sinne: das achte North American New Music Festival, in Frankfurter allgemeine Zeitung, June 7, 1990, 1 leaf (Box 6, Folder 356)
  - 1991, I.; Folders 357-361
    - State University of New York at Buffalo. News Bureau Ninth North American New Music Festival to feature dozens of new music idioms, mediums and performers, [news release], February 28, 1991, 3 leaves (Box 6, Folder 357)
    - North American New Music Festival 9th annual: the North American New Music Festival: April 18-24, 1991, circa April 1, 1991, 1 poster: printed black, white, aqua, and lavender; 50 x 43 cm. (Box 6, Folder 358)
      Program schedule and composer profiles printed on reverse.
    - Trotter, Herman New-music festival stays vital, in Buffalo News, April 14, 1991, 4 leaves (Box 6, Folder 359)
    - Putnam, Thomas Combination game: premiere of John Cage's 'Europera' combines singers, victrola and nostalgia, in Buffalo News, April 19, 1991, 2 leaves (Box 6, Folder 360)
    - Gaub, Eugene Minstrels successful in diversity of styles, in Buffalo News, April 24, 1991, 2 leaves (Box 6, Folder 361)
  - 1992, J.; Folders 362-380
    - State University of New York at Buffalo. News Bureau New music festival presents opera, symphony, Earle Brown and a wide range of percussion performances, [news release], March 10, 1992, 3 leaves (Box 6, Folder 362)
    - North American New Music Festival 10th annual North American New Music Festival: April 3-11, 1992, [program booklet], circa March 20, 1992, 32 p.: ill., ports.; 35 x 15 cm. (Box 6, Folder 363)
    - Grosvenor Society Give me a break: a lunchtime series of free noon hour concerts..., [brochure], circa March 20, 1992, 1 leaf (Box 6, Folder 364)
    - Trotter, Herman Nine-day new music festival builds on past, in Buffalo News, March 29, 1992, 2 leaves (Box 6, Folder 365)
    - Concerts at the Burchfield Art Center, [postcard], circa April 1, 1992, 1 leaf (Box 6, Folder 366)
    - State University of New York at Buffalo Classics on campus: Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra, [promotional flyer], circa Apri. 1, 1992, 1 leaf (Box 6, Folder 367)
    - Shea's Buffalo playbill for a production of Karol Szymanowski's opera, King Roger, vol. 18, no. 20, April 1992, 80 p.: ill., ports.; 22 cm. (Box 6, Folder 368)
    - Trotter, Herman Polish opera 'Roger' splendidly projected, in Buffalo News, April 4, 1992, 2 leaves (Box 6, Folder 369)
    - Trotter, Herman Lots of sounds produce little music, in Buffalo News, April 5, 1992, 2 leaves (Box 6, Folder 370)
    - Yadzinski, Edward The art of the composer, [program notes], April 5, 1992, 3 leaves (Box 6, Folder 371)
    - Sedlak, Lynna Control, respect typify Winds of Change, in Buffalo News, April 6, 1992, 2 leaves (Box 6, Folder 372)
    - Trotter, Herman Ganz spans centuries in new-music festival, in Buffalo News, April 7, 1992, 2 leaves (Box 6, Folder 373)
    - Young, Kenneth 'Birthday' music holds a touch of drama, in Buffalo News, April 7, 1992, 2 leaves (Box 6, Folder 374)
    - Putnam, Thomas Back to nature via computer: human voice, piano and violin spar with machine, in Buffalo News, April 9, 1992, 2 leaves (Box 6, Folder 375)
    - Sedlak, Lynna Winning hands, in Buffalo News, April 10, 1992, 2 leaves (Box 6, Folder 376)
    - Trotter, Herman Performance thrills with organ opus, in Buffalo News, April 11, 1992, 2 leaves (Box 6, Folder 377)
    - Young, Kenneth Percussionist's opener strikes a stunning effect, in Buffalo News, April 12, 1992, 2 leaves (Box 6, Folder 378)
    - Putnam, Thomas Puppet theater with music proves popular at festival, in Buffalo News, April 12, 1992, 2 leaves (Box 6, Folder 379)
    - Trotter, Herman Pianist's sensitivity to composers' styles rivets audience, in Buffalo News, April 12, 1992, 2 leaves (Box 6, Folder 380)
  - 1993, K.; Folders 381-382
    - North American New Music Festival Gala 10th anniversary: North American new music festival 1983-1993, [program booklet], circa October 15, 1993, 24 p.: ill., ports.; 26 cm. (Box 6, Folder 381)
    - Three articles from Buffalo News, October 31, 1993 Putnam, Thomas Hallwalls' ambience complements Cage's works, Sedlak, Lynna Gamelan ensemble excels in exploratory program, Trotter, Herman Harrison's works prove both eclectic, pleasurable (Box 6, Folder 382)
  - 1995, L.; Folders 383-385
    - Donovan, Patricia Hallwalls' ambience complements Cage's works. Gamelan ensemble excels in exploratory program, in Reporter, January 19, 1995, 3 leaves (Box 6, Folder 383)
    - North American New Music Festival North American New Music Festival, [display advertisement], circa February 9, 1995, 1 leaf (Box 6, Folder 384)
    - Mann, Jordan Songs and music from Turtle Island, in Spectrum, circa February 20, 1995, 2 leaves (Box 6, Folder 385)
- Funding Agencies, 1986-1993, III.; Folders 386-442
  Correspondence, grant applications, notes, reports on prospective funders, and similar materials related to financial support.
  Arranged alphabetically by name of funding source or subject.
  - British Council 1988, 2 leaves (Box 7, Folder 386)
  - British Council 1989, 6 leaves (Box 7, Folder 387)
  - British Council 1990, 1 leaf (Box 7, Folder 388)
  - Canadian Consulate General 1985, 1 leaf (Box 7, Folder 389)
  - Canadian Consulate General 1986, 2 leaves (Box 7, Folder 390)
  - Canadian Consulate General 1988, 8 leaves (Box 7, Folder 391)
  - Canadian Consulate General 1989, 13 leaves (Box 7, Folder 392)
  - Canadian Consulate General 1990, 5 leaves (Box 7, Folder 393)
  - Canadian Consulate General 1992, 1 leaf (Box 7, Folder 394)
  - Chase Lincoln First Bank 1988, 1 leaf (Box 7, Folder 395)
  - Graduate Student Association (State University of New York at Buffalo) 1987 and undated, 10 leaves (Box 7, Folder 396)
  - Graduate Student Association (State University of New York at Buffalo) 1988, 6 leaves (Box 7, Folder 397)
  - Graduate Student Association (State University of New York at Buffalo) 1989, 5 leaves (Box 7, Folder 398)
  - Graduate Student Association (State University of New York at Buffalo) 1990, 5 leaves (Box 7, Folder 399)
  - Graduate Student Association (State University of New York at Buffalo) 1992, 4 leaves (Box 7, Folder 400)
  - Mary Duke Biddle Foundation 1988, 6 leaves (Box 7, Folder 401)
  - Meet the Composer, Inc. 1983, 9 leaves (Box 7, Folder 402)
    Musicians named within this folder: Austin, Babbitt, Casavant, Chadabe, Dodge, Marcus, Montague, Moore, Rolnick, Simons, Truax
  - Meet the Composer, Inc. 1984, 23 leaves (Box 7, Folder 403)
    Musicians named within this folder: Bergamo, Biscardi, Celli, Davis, Galás, Gordon, Moss, Ortiz, Ruders, Russell, Zwilich
  - Meet the Composer, Inc. 1985, 34 leaves (Box 7, Folder 404)
    Musicians named within this folder: Carl, Daugherty, Davis, De Mare, Foss, Genge, Jaffe, Knussen, Landy, Levick, Mellnäs, Moravec, Nancarrow, Rasmussen, Rea, Rzewski, Sellars, Steiger, Stock, Thomson, Thow
  - Meet the Composer, Inc. 1986, 3 leaves (Box 7, Folder 405)
    Musicians named within this folder: Carl, Genge, Nancarrow, Rea
  - Meet the Composer, Inc. 1987, 14 leaves (Box 7, Folder 406)
    Musicians named within this folder: Aitkin, Bennett, Cage, Chadabe, Druckman, Felder, Glass, Hassell, Hiller, Kagel, Knussen, Leon, Luening, Morrill, Pennycook, Perle, Rudders, Shapey, Truax, Vigeland
  - Meet the Composer, Inc. 1988, 11 leaves (Box 7, Folder 407)
    Musicians named within this folder: Arcuri, Bartlett, Bennett, Carter, Chadabe, Emery, Felder, Laske, Leon, Metz, Ortiz, Schwartz, Swartz, Torke
  - Meet the Composer, Inc. 1989, 5 leaves and 1 booklet (Box 7, Folder 408)
    Musicians named within this folder: Crumb, Daugherty, Hyla, Ince, Kryszak
  - Meet the Composer, Inc. 1990, 11 leaves and 1 booklet (Box 7, Folder 409)
    Musicians named within this folder: Bennet, Degazio, Derome, García, Germani, Kikaukaun, La Barbara, Lucier, McCandless, Monahan, Montague, Mott, Schwartz, Sun Ra, Truax, Vigeland, Young
  - Meet the Composer, Inc. 1992, 27 leaves (Box 7, Folder 410)
    Musicians named within this folder: Brown, Chadabe, Jaffe, Pugliese, Riley, Scheidt, Tudor, Vérin
  - Mid-Atlantic States Arts Consortium 1985, 17 leaves (Box 7, Folder 411)
  - National Endowment for the Arts 1983, 3 leaves (Box 7, Folder 412)
  - National Endowment for the Arts 1985, 9 leaves and 1 booklet (Box 7, Folder 413)
  - National Endowment for the Arts 1986, 8 leaves (Box 7, Folder 414)
  - National Endowment for the Arts 1987, 18 leaves (Box 7, Folder 415)
  - National Endowment for the Arts 1988, 15 leaves (Box 7, Folder 416)
  - National Endowment for the Arts 1989, 18 leaves (Box 7, Folder 417)
  - National Endowment for the Arts 1990, 13 leaves (Box 7, Folder 418)
  - National Endowment for the Arts 1991, 17 leaves (Box 7, Folder 419)
  - National Endowment for the Arts 1992, 12 leaves (Box 7, Folder 420)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities 1984, 1 leaf (Box 7, Folder 421)
  - New York Council for the Humanities 1988, 5 leaves (Box 7, Folder 422)
  - New York Foundation for the Arts. Artists' Fellowship Program 1985, 4 leaves (Box 8, Folder 423)
  - Ontario House Common New York 1992, 1 leaves (Box 8, Folder 424)
  - Quebec Government House 1987-1988, 2 leaves (Box 8, Folder 425)
  - State University of New York. Research Foundation. Grant application 1985?, 16 leaves (Box 8, Folder 426)
  - State University of New York. Research Foundation. [Printed output from grantor database] 1988, 13 leaves (Box 8, Folder 427)
  - State University of New York at Buffalo. Canadian-American Studies Committee 1986, 2 leaves (Box 8, Folder 428)
  - State University of New York at Buffalo. Canadian-American Studies Committee 1988, 6 leaves (Box 8, Folder 429)
  - State University of New York at Buffalo. Canadian-American Studies Committee 1989, 1 leaf (Box 8, Folder 430)
  - State University of New York at Buffalo. Canadian-American Studies Committee 1990, 13 leaves (Box 8, Folder 431)
  - State University of New York at Buffalo. Canadian-American Studies Committee 1992, 22 leaves (Box 8, Folder 432)
  - State University of New York at Buffalo. Conferences in the Disciplines 1985, 4 leaves (Box 8, Folder 433)
  - State University of New York at Buffalo. Conferences in the Disciplines 1986, 15 leaves (Box 8, Folder 434)
  - State University of New York at Buffalo. Conferences in the Disciplines 1987, 11 leaves (Box 8, Folder 435)
  - State University of New York at Buffalo. Conferences in the Disciplines 1988, 15 leaves (Box 8, Folder 436)
  - State University of New York at Buffalo. Conferences in the Disciplines 1989, 20 leaves (Box 8, Folder 437)
  - State University of New York at Buffalo. Conferences in the Disciplines 1990, 15 leaves (Box 8, Folder 438)
  - State University of New York at Buffalo. Conferences in the Disciplines 1992, 10 leaves (Box 8, Folder 439)
  - State University of New York at Buffalo. Conferences in the Disciplines undated, 3 leaves (Box 8, Folder 440)
  - State University of New York at Buffalo. Faculty of Arts and Letters. Office of the Dean 1985 and 1988, 5 leaves (Box 8, Folder 441)
  - Sub Board I, Inc. (State University of New York at Buffalo) 1987-1988, 5 leaves (Box 8, Folder 442)
- Festival operations 1983-1993, IV.; Folders 443-511
  Materials related to planning and production of the Festivals.
  Arranged into four subseries.